uglii.com 2012-10-15

# Privacy Statement - Uglii

**Date: 24th September 2010**

### **Scope**

In this Privacy Statement “we”, “our”, and “us” refers to SISS Business Systems Pty Ltd (ACN 085 265 309) and each of its related entities.

At SISS we value the protection and security of your personal information. As an Australian company we are bound by the Privacy Act 1998 (Cth) and the National Privacy Principles (“NPPs”). As an international company, we also abide by the _U.S. Department of Commerce Safe Harbor Program_ (“Safe Harbour provisions”).

SISS’s Privacy Policy covers the collection, use, and disclosure of personal information that may be collected by SISS or on its behalf anytime you become involved with us, and our Global Partners, National Partners and Affiliates (“our representatives”).

Please take some time to carefully consider our information practices and how they might impact on you. We respect the privacy and confidentiality of your personal information.

### Collection

**What personal information we collect**

We need certain information so we can provide you with our services and products. This may include your name, address, phone number and other information for payment or identification purposes. What we collect depends on the service and product that we provide for you. If you do not provide us with the information asked, we may not be able to provide the service you want.

**How we collect personal information**

##### We collect information in a number of ways, including:

  * Directly from you when you visit us, our website or the websites of our representatives.
  * When you provide us with information for the purposes of registering with us or through our representatives.
  * When you provide us with personal information for transactions carried out by you, e.g. purchase our products and services. Or,
  * When you speak with our Media & Marketing staff.

**Why we collect personal information**

##### We collect your personal information primarily because it enables us to:

  * allow access and use of our website, products and services
  * to verify the identity of people and businesses who use our website, products and services
  * administer and manage the our website, products and services
  * deliver a superior level of customer service and to generate competition to encourage the highest standard of relevant information about your businesses, products and services
  * provide personalised website information about us, for you and to provide you with information you may wish to post on your own website
  * respond to your queries or complaints and general customer service
  * comply with laws and regulatory requirements
  * comply with our compliance and risk management policies and procedures
  * supply to you products that you purchase
  * collect and make payments from you
  * research and development for our products
  * train our staff
  * keep you posted on marketing announcements that you might like to hear about. If you do not want us to send you the latest information on products please email [unsubscribe@uglii.com](mailto:unsubscribe@uglii.com).

### Use and Disclosure

**Use**

##### We may use your personal information for purposes related to those listed above. We will not use your personal information unless it is for:

  * a purpose you know about
  * a purpose that you would reasonably expect
  * a purpose required or permitted by the law
  * a purpose you consented to.

**Disclosure Generally**

We take your privacy very seriously. We will not sell or rent your personal information to others.

**Disclosure within our Group**

To help us provide superior service, your personal information may be shared with legal entities within the SISS group globally who will take steps to safeguard it in accordance with our privacy policy.

We may disclose your information to third parties such as our agents or contractors to provide you with our products and services. We have confidentiality clauses within our services agreements and/or confidentiality agreements with our third parties providers and suppliers to ensure our confidential information and your personal information are protected.

**With our service providers, vendors, and strategic partners**

There are also times when it may be advantageous for SISS to make certain personal information about you available to companies that SISS has a strategic relationship with or that perform work for SISS to provide products and services to you on our behalf. These companies are also obligated to protect your personal information in accordance with SISS’s policies, or have similar privacy protection policies, except if we inform you otherwise at the time of collection.

**Disclosure for Legal Reasons**

We may disclose your personal information if required to do so by law, in connection with any legal proceedings or prospective legal proceedings, and in order to establish, exercise or defend any legal rights.

We may also disclose information about you if we determine that for national security, law enforcement, or other issues of public importance, disclosure is necessary.

**Publicly displayed information is public**

##### If you use a bulletin board or chat room on an SISS or Uglii website you should be aware that any information you submit to these forums:

  * is visible to other users.
  * can be read, collected, or used by other individuals to send you unsolicited messages.
  * may be collected by others (including SISS) and made publically available.

SISS is not responsible for the personally identifiable information you choose to submit in these forums.

### Integrity of your personal information

We want to ensure that your personal information is complete, accurate and up-to-date. We may contact you to advise us of any changes to your personal information and ask you to contact us if you believe that the information we have about you is not accurate.

### Security

**Storage**

We store personal information electronically, paper-based files and other recording methods.

Information that we collect may be stored and processed in and transferred between any of the countries in which we operate to enable the use of the information in accordance with SISS’ Privacy Policy.

In addition, personal information that you submit for publication on this website will be published on the internet and may be available around the world.

You agree to such cross-border transfers of personal information.

**How we protect your personal information**

We will take reasonable steps to prevent any loss, misuse, unauthorised access or modification of your personal information.

We maintain both physical and electronic security procedures to manage and protect the use and storage of your personal information.

We will store all the personal information you provide on secure servers and information relating to electronic transactions entered into via our website will be protected by encryption technology.

### Access to your personal information

You may request access to your personal information by contacting us. If we are unable to meet your request for access, we will let you know why.

We may need to verify your identity and may charge a service fee for retrieving and sending information to you. We will advise you of any service fee at the time.

You can help us ensure that your contact information and preferences are accurate, complete, and up to date by checking your online account and or you can request a copy of your personal information by contacting us at the email address below.

### International users

Whether your personal information is from or is disclosed outside Australia, we will ensure your personal information will be protected by a law or in a contract similar to the privacy principles stated here and contained the NPP’s in Australia.

We also abide by the safe harbour framework set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use, and retention of personal information collected from the European Union. The following link provides more information about the _U.S. Department of Commerce Safe Harbor Program._

Our website has links to the sites of other companies. SISS is not responsible for their privacy practices. We encourage you to learn about the privacy policies of those companies.

### Cookies and other technologies

We collect activity information on our website through the use of “cookies” and other technologies to help us understand which parts of our websites are the most popular, where our visitors are going, and how much time they spend there.

**Cookies**

A “cookie” is a small text file placed on your computer by a webpage server which can then be accessed by our web servers.

We also use cookies and other technologies to make sure that our online advertising is bringing customers to our products and services.

We use cookies and other technologies to study traffic patterns on our website, to make it even more rewarding as well as to study the effectiveness of our customer communications. We also use cookies to customise your experience and provide greater convenience each time you interact with us.

If, however, you prefer not to enable cookies, you can configure your web browsers to refuse to accept cookies, however, this may mean you may not be able to make full use of our website as certain features of the SISS website will not be available once cookies are disabled.

**Log files**

As is true of most websites, we gather certain information automatically and store it in log files. This information includes Internet Protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, Internet Service Provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, and click stream data.

We use this information, which does not identify individual users, to analyse trends, to administer the site, to track users, movements around the site and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole. We will not use the information collected to market directly to that person.

**Click-through URL**

In some of our email messages we use a “click-through URL” linked to content on the SISS website. When customers click one of these URLs, they pass through our web server before arriving at the destination web page. We track this click-through data to help us determine interest in particular topics and measure the effectiveness of our customer communications. If you prefer not to be tracked simply avoid clicking text or graphic links in the email.

**Pixel Tags**

In addition, we use pixel tags – tiny graphic images – to tell us what parts of our website customers have visited or to measure the effectiveness of searches customers perform on our site.

Pixel tags also enable us to send email messages in a format customers can read. Pixel tags tell us whether emails have been opened to ensure that we’re sending only messages that are of interest to our customers. We may use this information to reduce or eliminate messages sent to a customer.

### Changes to the Privacy Statement and our Privacy Policy

We will make changes to this Statement and our Privacy Policy from time to time. Check this site for the most up-to-date version of our Privacy Statement.

You should check this page occasionally to ensure you are familiar with any changes.

### Unsubscribe

You may be contacted for the purposes of customer service or to be notified about new promotions, newsletters, marketing campaigns and similar material. If you do not wish to receive this information, you can unsubscribe to our updates by sending us an email to [unsubscribe@uglii.com](mailto:unsubscribe@uglii.com).

### Further Information

If you have any questions about this Privacy Statement, our treatment of your personal information, have a complaint, or want a copy of our Privacy Policy “please write to our Privacy Officer” [privacy@uglii.com](mailto:privacy@uglii.com)

We will try to resolve your complaint internally. Should we not resolve your complaint satisfactorily, you may wish to apply to the Privacy Commission in your country.  
Complaints can also be lodged in Australia with the Federal Privacy Commissioner on +61 1300 363 992.
